jobee.pk 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Jobee.Pk

Last updated: August 24, 2016

Jobee.pk ("us", "we", or "our") operates the www.jobee.pk website (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. We share your information to various customers / companies seeking employees or employers. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at www.jobee.pk

**Information Collection And Use**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, phone number, postal address, other information ("Personal Information”), work history, experience, education, etc. We collect this information for the purpose of providing the Service, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries, servicing your purchase orders, and share it with companies / users who have access to our employer services. We share this information with companies / users that re hiring so that we can serve the purpose of our site by connecting professionals with companies. Please keep in mind that any information contained within your profile is shared with employers / customers who have access to employer services on our website. We also use this information to improve Our services. 

We also collect: 

  * Username and password for the account you create with us
  * We keep record of your Job search behavior and preferences, and a record of the searches that you make on Jobee.PK. We do this in order to present you with job recommendations and other services.
  * If you’ve authorized for us to access your social media profile, we collect information to share with companies / users using our employer services. If you’ve shared a facebook, google+, or twitter account, the users and companies with access to your profiles will be able to view it.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

  * To connect you with companies / customers seeking employees. These companies will be able to view the information you have created within your profile with Jobee.pk.
  * To connect Employers or Users with access to our employer services with user profiles within our system.
  * To personalize user's experience and to allow us to match you to jobs or services that fit your needs based on our recorded data on your preferences and searches. 
  * To improve our website.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products.
  * To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

**Sharing of Information**

When you join Jobee.pk or apply for a job through us, we share your Personal Information with employer customers. These customers may use this information to evaluate you for jobs and contact you. These customers may also store your information and in such cases, the use of this information will be subjected to the privacy policy of that company. We also share employer customer’s information with job seeker customers. Our employer customers are able to post jobs on our website that we share with our job seeker customers. Jobee.PK will not be responsible for misuse for this information stored by the Job seeker customer or the employer customer.

When you apply for a job through Jobee.PK, this information becomes a part of our database and it might also become a part of the employer’s database. In the case that it becomes a part of the employers database, the use of the information will be subjected to the privacy policy of that employer / user.

When you post a job on Jobee.PK, this information becomes a part of our database and it might also become a part of some other user’s database. In the case that it become a part of a user’s database, Jobee.PK is not responsible on how this information is used by the users.

Users should keep in mind that when they display personal information through Jobee.PK, this information can be accessed, collected, and used by others. It could result in third parties attempting to contact this user. Jobee.PK is not responsible for unsolicited contact or message requests from third parties. 

At times, we may aggregate data to provide our employer customers or our Job Seeker customers with reporting to help serve them better and better our services.

**How do we protect visitor information?**

Members are our top priority. We will guard your information as much as we can while being a professional platform for Job Seekers and Employers / Companies. Please note that once you create your Jobee Profile, your information will be available to anyone who has a link to your profile / resume and also any user / companies with access to our platform through our employer services. If you are an employer or company advertising on our website, the job information and company information you provide is public and will be shared with users and on any other platforms that we may see fit.

Please note that though we verify companies that are willing to send us their CNIC or other government issued ID, there are many companies who choose to use our employer services without going through our verification requirement. These are marked as “Unverified.” Jobee.pk cannot be held responsible for any false representation. Whether a company is verified or not, we encourage users to always use discretion and caution. Being an online platform, we cannot be held responsible for any mishaps. We take our users' privacy very seriously; if you see any questionable behavior, please contact us immediately and report it. 

**Log Data**

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie. If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Service and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

**Service Providers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose. 

**Compliance With Laws**

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.

**Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you. 

**International Transfer**

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction. If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

**Links To Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. 

**Children's Privacy**

Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access our Service. Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children"). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. 

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of August 24, 2016 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.
